imarcgroup.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy | IMARC Group

We value your privacy rights and take utmost care to keep your personal information secure. The following Privacy Policy explains how IMARC (“we”, “us” or “our”) use, protect and disclose the information provided by you. All our employees and business partners are strictly required to follow our Privacy Policy. 

Please note that by visiting and using [ www.imarcgroup.com ](https://www.imarcgroup.com/)(“the Site”), you agree to follow this Policy and other Terms of Use.

#### Collection and Use of information

We may monitor your sessions and collect anonymous information while you use the Site. This information is collected solely in order to improve the user experience on the Site. 

You may provide us with personal information about yourself while filling certain forms on the Site, signing up for subscriptions, contacting us by phone or via email and using our services. This personal information can include your name, address, email ID, phone number and other identification and financial details. This information is used by us in order to provide you with our services, solve your queries, process your orders and send you promotional emails that you may have signed up for. We do not share any of the anonymous or personal information collected by us with third-party websites for any commercial or promotional use. 

#### Sharing and Disclosure

Under specific circumstances, we may need to share your personal information with our employees or our business partners in order to provide you with the required services. However, we shall not do so without first notifying you. We do not sell, rent, trade or share any information provided by you with other organisations for commercial or promotional purposes. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information under certain legal situations without giving any prior notice. 

#### Third-Party Links

The Site may contain links which will redirect you to certain third-party websites. We do not make any representations about these websites or endorse them. As these sites cannot be subject to this Privacy Policy, we recommend that you read their Terms of Use and other policies before using their services. We have no control and take no responsibilities regarding the content on these websites. You agree that if you access these websites, you do so at your own risk. 

#### Security

In order to safeguard your personal information from loss, alteration, misuse or damage, we follow generally accepted technological and operational security measures. However, in spite of these security measures we cannot guarantee the safety of your personal information. You agree that you will not hold IMARC responsible for any breach of security or loss of information. 

#### Modifications

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without any prior notice to you. The revisions will be updated on this page and shall be in effect immediately. You are advised to reviews the Policy from time-to-time in order to stay abreast with any changes. 

#### Cookie Policy

A cookie, which is a small text file that gets saved on your deice after you give your consent. We employ cookies to record your preferences and monitor session data in order to enhance site responsiveness. We use this data to better understand your likings and preferences enabling us to offer better services by providing you information that suits your needs. The cookies give us no access to any other information that you choose not to share including any of your personal information or files. You may, at any time, disable cookies whenever you visit the site, however, doing so may limit your access to site. 

#### GDPR Policy

General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) policy forms part of the new structure to protect personal information of European Union citizens. It lays down new standards for data gathering, storage and use by all firms functioning in the area. We comply with the GDPR policy and remain dedicated to complete transparency in our operations and protection of your personal information. Our data privacy and security team work constantly to meet the guidelines of the new data protection policy.
